Resume



Personal Information

Name Andrew Klimenko

Date of Birth 26.04.1989

Place of Birth Zaporizhzhya

Marital Status Single

Overview

I'm a developer from Ukraine with solid front-end experience and a huge pack of projects behind my back. I am strong at frontend development such as Angular 2+, Angular Material, Bootstrap, PrimeNG, TypeScript, etc and am always ready to deepen my knowledge in these technologies. I also work with different kinds of API's as Google, Twitter, Instagram etc.

I have more than two years of experience in web development. For the last few years I have mainly worked with Shopify (Liquid) and Angular 2+.

I am experienced in the work with git versions control system as well as with the npm. I have also got experience in the usage of gulp application.

Am always ready to face up the work of any complexity.

Education

2010 - 2011 Zaporizhzhia National University

Faculty of foreign languages

Bachelor degree

2006 - 2011 Classical Private University

Tourism and Hotel business

Master degree

Work Experience

August 2017 - February 2018 ITMaster, Zaporizhzhya

Worked through Agile process with team on estimation and meeting sprint commitments. Developed new features and provided maintenance and enhancements development work with a team of full stack developers to analyze, design, code

and test multiple components of application code.

August 2015 - August 2017 JSNinjas, Zaporizhzhya

I developed marvelous user interfaces and admin ones, provide various solutions as for the optimization of the work

and look of the site as well.

Skills

Programming HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, LESS/SASS, Angular 2+, Liquid

(Shopify CMS), npm, gulp

Foreign Languages

English Intermediate

Russian Bilingual

Ukrainian Bilingual

Contact Information

Address Ukraine, Zaporizhzhya

Phone +380991508500

E-Mail tisandrii@gmail.com

Site https://whoisandrii.github.io

Other

Hobbies Traveling, Music, Fitness, Cinema